[
  {
    "front": "maintenant",
    "back": "今"
  },
  {
    "front": "personne",
    "back": "人"
  },
  {
    "front": "jour, journée",
    "back": "日"
  },
  {
    "front": "mois, lune",
    "back": "月"
  },
  {
    "front": "feu",
    "back": "火"
  },
  {
    "front": "eau",
    "back": "水"
  },
  {
    "front": "arbre, bois",
    "back": "木"
  },
  {
    "front": "or, argent, monnaie",
    "back": "金"
  },
  {
    "front": "terre, sol",
    "back": "土"
  },
  {
    "front": "origine, source, vrai, livre",
    "back": "本"
  }
]
